<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Narun Raman</title>
    <link>www.narunraman.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Narun Raman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:31:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.narunraman.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>www.narunraman.com/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 12:42:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.narunraman.com/photos/</guid>
      <description> galleries:
gallery number one 1:
row one in gallery one    { url: &amp;lsquo;1.jpg&amp;rsquo;, alt: &amp;lsquo;alt 1&amp;rsquo;}    row two in gallery one    { url: &amp;lsquo;2.jpg&amp;rsquo;, alt: &amp;lsquo;alt 2&amp;rsquo;} { url: &amp;lsquo;3.jpg&amp;rsquo;, alt: &amp;lsquo;alt 3&amp;rsquo;}    gallery number two 2:
row one in gallery two    { url: &amp;lsquo;4.jpg&amp;rsquo;, alt: &amp;lsquo;alt 4&amp;rsquo;} { url: &amp;lsquo;5.jpg&amp;rsquo;, alt: &amp;lsquo;alt 5&amp;rsquo;}    other front matter like title, &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narun Raman</title>
      <link>www.narunraman.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:31:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.narunraman.com/about/</guid>
      <description>a little about me  I pronounce my name like Maroon (with an N) Ramen &amp;ndash; quite an unappetizing sight.1 Having said that, please feel free to email me pictures of oddly colored noodles that you have made or found:
narunram [at] cs [dot] ubc [dot] ca.
narunram [at] cs [dot] ubc [dot] ca. -- at] ```cs``` [dot] ```ubc``` [dot] ```ca```. -- I am currently a Master&amp;rsquo;s student under Kevin Leyton-Brown pursuing Computer Science at the University of British Columbia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>personal</title>
      <link>www.narunraman.com/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.narunraman.com/bio/</guid>
      <description>Best Places to Eat Ratna Cafe (Chennai, India): Probably the best sambar vada in the world and decent filter coffee.
per se Social Corner (Vancouver, Canada): The best pizza I have ever had in my life.
Elephant (Vancouver, Canada): Their omakase (really a price fixe menu) is the best in Vancouver.
Dishoom (London, England) Best indian food outside of India. Their okra fries are excellent.
Where to Eat and Drink    British Columbia    Maenam (Vancouver) Little Bird Dim Sum (Vancouver) Yuwa Japanese Cuisine (Vancouver) Casareccio (Vancouver) Tameki Sushi (Vancouver) Mon Pitou Bistro &amp;amp; Bakery (Vancouver) acquafarina (Vancouver) per se Social Corner (Vancouver) Autostrada Osteria Downtown (Vancouver) Lupo (Vancouver) Kissa Tanto (Vancouver) Pizzeria Farina (Vancouver) Khaghan (Vancouver) Fable Diner (Vancouver) Earnest Ice Cream (Vancouver) Sing Sing (Vancouver) Brassneck Brewery (Vancouver) Beta5 Chocolates (Vancouver) Elephant (Vancouver) Tandoori Flame (Surrey) Green Lettuce (Surrey) Fox &amp;amp; Oak (Squamish) Green Olive Market and Cafe (Squamish) Raudz Regional Table (Kelowna)      California    Ettan (Palo Alto) Pasta Moon (Half Moon Bay) Taqueria El Farolito (San Francisco) DamnFine (San Francisco) Plow (San Francisco) ROOH SF (San Francisco) Mensho Tokyo SF (San Francisco) La Taqueria (San Francisco) La Note (Berkeley) Spoon Korean Bistro (Berkeley)      Utah   - Ivy &amp; Varley (Salt Lake City) - Lake Effect (Salt Lake City) - Banbury Cross Donuts (Salt Lake City)     Iowa   - Pullman Bar and Grill (Iowa City) - Big Grove Brewery &amp; Taproom (Iowa City)     Minnesota   - Kumar&#39;s (Apple Valley) - Hola Arepa (Minneapolis) - Hen House Eatery (Minneapolis) - Sen Yai Sen Lek (Minneapolis)     Wisconsin   - A Pig in a Fur Coat (Madison) - Bradbury&#39;s Coffee (Madison) - Marigold Kitchen (Madison) - Cento (Madison) - Cafe Hollander (Hilldale)     Spain   - La Papardella (Valencia)     England   - Bibimbap House (Cambridge) - Trockel, Ulmann &amp; Freunde (Cambridge) - Benet&#39;s Cafe (Cambridge) - Padella (London) - Round House (London) - Dishoom (London) - Veeraswamy (London) - Gymkhana (London) - Homeslice Neal&#39;s Yard (London) - Udderlicious (London) - Pizza Union (London)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
